Details

shashank201011@gmail.com 07858280680

shashankravikumar.netlify.app/

Links

Personal Portfolio

Github

Linkedin

Dribbble

Skills

Programming

ReactJS

HTML5

CSS/Sass

Python

Java

C++

MySQL

JavaScript

Design

Figma

Adobe XD

Photoshop

Photoshop

Premiere Pro

Lightroom

Illustrator

Software

GitHub

Visual Studio Code

Trello

Microsoft Office

Netlify

Interests

Technology

Exercising

MMA

Music

Shashank Ravikumar

Profile

Computer Science graduate at the University of East Anglia with the academic qualifications and practical experiences to conceive, design, execute web apps within project parameters. Possess a solid foundation in coding languages, software tools, human-computer interaction, and wireframe development. Partnered with high-powered design teams to contribute to product development and implementation strategy. I am highly motivated and very imaginative by finding inspirations in everyday things, pushing my boundaries and allowing myself to think out of the box.

Employment History

Customer Sales Advisor at NHS Tack and Trace, SITEL

DECEMBER 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2021

- Providing an excellent customer service experience for our clients
- Solve customer issues with their computers
- Scheduling appointments for clients
- Managing multiple software programs at a time
- · Kept accurate records of client's interactions
- Determine charges for plans purchased with us or services scheduled

Customer Sales Representative at Domino's Pizza, London

MARCH 2020 — JULY 2020

- Charted a successful course for customer satisfaction by responding to customer inquiries, resolving concerns, and taking orders in a deadline-drive environment.
- Assisted with food preparation as necessary.
- Ensured customer-facing and other areas were clean and sanitary by organizational and regulatory health standards.
- Utilized systems to allow customers to place orders both through phone and in-store

Mail Sorter at Royal Mail, London

JULY 2019 — DECEMBER 2019

- Organized the sorting of mail, packets, parcels, and other deliverable items
- Ensured accurate, efficient, and compliant separation of 1st Class and 2nd Class mail.
- $\bullet \quad \hbox{Oversaw categories of items (Standard, Next Day, Signed For, Recorded)}.$
- Aligned item dispatching with the appropriate timetable.
- Performed additional tasks in collaboration with other colleagues as necessary

Education

Computer Science, University of East Anglia, Norwich

SEPTEMBER 2017 — JULY 2020

Relevant Course:

- Human-Computer interaction
- Web development
- Networks

- Database Systems
- Database and Architectures
- Object-Oriented Programming

GCE A LEVEL, The Forest Academy, London

SEPTEMBER 2015 — JULY 2017

Relevant Grades: Mathematics (B) Physics (C) BTEC Business (DD*)

GCSE'S, Beal High School, London

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JULY 2015

Relevant Grades: 8 Subjects A* – C grades, including English (C) & Maths (B)

Projects

Links to some of my work can be found on <u>shashankravikumar.netlify.app</u> work and more details can be provided by getting in contact with me.

Courses

UX/UI COURSE IN USER EXPERIENCE DESIGN ESSENTIALS, UDEMY

NOVEMBER 2020 — JANUARY 2021